patchmypc.net 2019-10-09

# Privacy Policy | Patch My PC

**  
Patch My PC, LLC**  
Last Updated: September 8, 2019

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to [https://patchmypc.com](https://patchmypc.com/), [https://ideas.patchmypc.com](https://ideas.patchmypc.com/) (the “Site”, “Sites”, “Website”) and Patch My PC, LLC (“ **Patch My PC** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” “ **our** ,” or “ **ours** ”) and governs your use of our Website and Software and any other services we may offer through our Site or Software (collectively, the “ **System** ”) and describes data collection and usage. The Patch My PC website is a software and services site. By using the Patch My PC System, you consent to the data practices described in this privacy policy statement along with our [Terms of Service](https://patchmypc.com/terms-of-service).

Please note that the statements set forth under the headings “ **Simply put** ” are provided as a courtesy for your convenience and are not legally binding or otherwise designed to modify these Terms

Collection of your Personal Information | Sharing Information with Third Parties | Tracking User Behavior | Automatically Collected Information | Use of Cookies | Links | Security of your Personal Information | Children Under Thirteen | External Data Storage Sites | Changes to this Privacy Policy | Contact Information

By using Patch My PC’s website or services, you agree to our Privacy Policy and End User License Agreement.

In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Patch My PC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Patch My PC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

– First and Last Name  
– Mailing Address  
– E-mail Address  
– Phone Number  
– Employer  
– Job Title  
– Other information related to your form submissions and inquiries.

If you purchase Patch My PC’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Patch My PC’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

When you use our website and services, we store your contact and billing details for our records. For all visitors, we collect information like your browser type, the length of time you spend on the site, and some demographic data to help us learn more about our users.

Patch My PC collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Patch My PC may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Patch My PC and its affiliates.

Describes how we may use the collected information. 

 Patch My PC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Patch My PC may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Patch My PC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Patch My PC may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Patch My PC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Patch My PC; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Patch My PC, or the public.

We don’t sell or trade your contact information to other companies. We may share your account information if we are required to by law. We also collect certain tracking information about your activity on our website to personalize your experience and to improve our services.

Patch My PC may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Patch My PC, in order to determine what Patch My PC services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Patch My PC to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

We use Google Analytics for website usage tracking. Please see how Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites?hl=en>. Please see <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> for information about Google Analytics to better understand how cookies work and how to modify your browsers’ settings.

Browing usage is automatically collected using services such as [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites?hl=en) to improve our services.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Patch My PC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Patch My PC website.

The Patch My PC website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Patch My PC pages, or register with Patch My PC site or services, a cookie helps Patch My PC to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Patch My PC website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Patch My PC features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Patch My PC services or websites you visit.

We use cookies to personalize your website experience. If you don’t want to allow cookie usage, you can change your browser settings to refuse them. 

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

To improve your experience, our website will link to other third-party websites. We are not responsible for the content on those websites. 

Patch My PC secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Patch My PC uses the following methods for this purpose:

– SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

Patch My PC’s secure website helps to keep your personal information safe. 

Patch My PC does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

No one under 13 should use Patch My PC’s services.

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

We may use third-party hosting providers for our website.

Patch My PC may change the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time, and will always post the most up-to-date version on our website.

This is the most recent version of the privacy policy. If we change it, we’ll update it here.
